Federal Theatre Project Collection, 1935-1939: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Federal Theatre Project Collection
1935-1939
TC015
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections Rare Book Division One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
2.5 linear feet 1 archival box, 6 oversize flat boxes
Federal Theatre Project (U.S.).
The Federal Theatre Project Collection consists of bulletins, reports, speeches, catalogues, play programs, information releases, notices and reviews, clippings, protest leaflets, performance details, and other materials of the Federal Theatre Project established by the Works Progress Administration during the Depression, with Hallie Flanagan as the national director.
The Federal Theatre Project was established by the Works Progress Administration during the Depression, with Hallie Flanagan as the national director.
The collection consists of materials relating to Federal Theatre Project performances, including issues of Federal Theatre (the bulletin of the Federal Theatre Project), reports and speeches, catalogues, play programmes and notices (by state, Negro theatre, children's theatre, and marionettes), information releases, notices and reviews, newspaper clippings, and performance details. In addition, there is some correspondence on “The Edward Rice Case,” regarding Edward Le Roy Rice and his firing from the Project, and state and local historical records of the Works Progress Administration documenting play programs deposited in New York collections (1936).
Collection is open for research use.
Rice, Edward Le Roy, 1871- -- Career in theater.; Federal Music Project (U.S.); Children's plays, American -- 20th century.; Federal aid to the theater -- United States -- 20th century.; Puppets and puppet-plays -- United States -- 20th century.; Theater programs -- United States -- 20th century.; Theater/Film
- Series 1: Federal Theatre [Bulletin of the Federal Theatre Project], 1935 November 25-1937; portion of 1 box
  No arrangement action taken or arrangement information not recorded at the time of processing.
  - Volume I, Number 1, 1935 November 25; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Volume I, Number 2, 1935 December; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Volume I, Number 3, 1936 January; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume I, Number 4, 1936 January; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume I, Number 5, 1936; 3 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume I, Number 6, 1936; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume II, Number 1, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume II, Number 2, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume II, Number 3, 1937; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
  - Volume II, Number 4, 1937 April; 3 copies (Box 1)
  - Volume II, Number 5, 1937 June; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - First Federal summer Theatre... A Report, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - National Policy Board Agenda, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 1)
- Series 2: Reports and Speeches, 1935 October-1939 January; 2 folders
  - Brief by Hallie Flanagan before the Committee on Patents, House of Representatives on, 1938 February 8; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Statement by Hallie Flanagan on, 1936 February 17; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brief Review of the Federal Theatre Project, 1935 October-1939 January, prepared by the National Service Bureau, portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Unemployed Arts” article reprinted from Fortune, 1937 May; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Play Bureau reports, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Conference Report, 1936 July 22-24; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization Report, 1936 September; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Productivity and Service Review, 1936 January-December; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Play Bureau Script: R-U-R by Karel Capek, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Catalogues, 1937-1938; 1 folder
  - Catalogues, 1937-1938; 3 copies (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lists of publishers, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series 4: Play Programmes and Notices, 1919 January 10-1939; 2 boxes
  - Arizona, dates not examined; 1 folder
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, 12/12, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - California, 1938 August-1939 June 5; 2 folders
    - “High Tor”: Maxwell Anderson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Bird of Paradise”: Richard Walton Tully, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Prologue to Glory”: E. P. Conkle, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Sun Rises in the West”: Theodore Pezman, Rena Vale, and Donald A. Murry, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Having Wonderful Time”: Arthur Kober, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Two a Day”: Gene Stone and Jack Robison, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Big Blow”: Theodore Pratt, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Excursion”: Victor Wolfson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Merchant of Venice”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Richard II” and “Merchant of Venice”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Richard II” and “Hamlet”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Merchant of Venice” and “Richard II”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Taming of the Shrew”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Hamlet”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scenes from “Richard II” and “Midsummer Night's Dream”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Everyman,”, 1938 September 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, dates not examined; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, 10/12, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, 1938 August 1; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Myra Kinch Modern Dance Concert, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Nativity”: Gareth Hughes, 12/14, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Lady of Letters”: Turner Bullock, 1938 November; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Milky Way”: Lynn Root and Harry Clork, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Lady of Letters,”, 1938 August; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Lady of Letters,”, 8/25, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Alarm Clock”: Avery Hopwood, 8/16, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Post Road”: Wilbur Daniel Steele and Norma Mitchel, 10/18, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Penny Wise”: Jean Ferfuson Black, 3/9, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Mikado”: Gilbert and Sullivan, 1939 January 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Very Great Men”: A. E. Thomas and Jack Haussman, 9/22, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “It Might Happen to You”: Leon Lord, 4/15, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “I Want a Policeman”: Rufus King and Milton Lazarus, 9/8, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Day is Darkness”: George Fess, 1939 June 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Judgment Day”: Elmer Rice, 1938 August; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “See How They Run”: George M. Savage Jr, 1938 September; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “An Evening with Dunbar”: Paul Lawrence Dunbar, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “A Bill of Divorcement”: Clemence Dane, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Spirochete”: Arnold Sungaard, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Camel through the Needle's Eye”: Frantisek Langer, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Ninth Guest”: Owen Davis, 3/23, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Little Women”: Marian de Forest, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “A Moral Entertainment”: Richard Maibaum, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Mississippi Rainbow”: John Charles Brownell, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “One Third of a Nation”: Arthur Arent, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Nativity”: Gareth Hughes, 12/19, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “The Nativity”: Gareth Hughes, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Run, Little Chillun”: Hall Johnson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Run, Little Chillun”: Hall Johnson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Run, Little Chillun”: Hall Johnson, dates not examined; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Run, Little Chillun”: Hall Johnson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - “Night Must Fall”: Emyln Williams, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Colorado, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “Night Must Fall”: Emyln Williams, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “The Milky Way”: Lynn Root and Harry Clork, 1938 August; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “Criminal at Large”: Edgar Wallace, 1938 September; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “If Ye Break Faith”: Maria M. Coxe, 1938 November; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “Post Road”: Wilbur Daniel Steele and Norma Mitchell, 1938 November; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “The Dragon's Wishbone”: Joan and Michel Andrew Slane, 1938 October 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “Room Service”: John Murry and Allen Boretz, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - “Lady of Letters”: Turner Bullock, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut, 1919 January 10-1939 January 28; 1 folder
    - “Macbeth”: Shakespeare, 3/22, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “The Mad Hopes”: Romney Brent, 8/15, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “In Abraham's Bosom”: Paul Green, 9/7, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “In the Valley”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “Liliom”: Ferenc Molnar, 9/21, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “Haiti”: William du Bois, 10/26, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “Haiti”: William du Bois, 1938 November 9; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “Haiti”: William du Bois, circa 1919 January 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “One Third of a Nation”: Arthur Arent, 1938 January 19; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “One Third of a Nation”: Arthur Arent, 1939 January 20; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - “One Third of a Nation”: Arthur Arent, 1939 January 28; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Florida, 1919 September 19-1939 December 8; 1 folder
    - “The Bride the Sun Shines On”: Will Cotton, circa 1919 September 19; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Petrified Forest”: Robert Sherwood, 1938 October 17; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Hits and Highlights”, 1939 December 8; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “The Emperor's New Clothes”: Charlotte Charpenning, 1938 December 26; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Room Service”: John Murray and Allen Boretz, 1939 January 16; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “High Tor”: Maxwell Anderson, 1939 February 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “The Rise of Silas Lapham”: William Dean Howells, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “R-U-R”: Karel Capek, 1939 March; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “The Best Cure”: Belmont and Ashton, 1939 March 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Invitation to the Dance”: Johann Strauss, 1939 April 10; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Reward”: Ida Caminiti, 4/15, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “The Farmer takes a Wife”: Frank B. Elser and Marc Connelly, 1939 May 29; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - “Television”: Dorothea Thomas Lynch and William Tennyson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Georgia, 1938 January 24-1939 April 25; 1 folder
    - “Journey's End”: R. C. Sherriff, 1938 January 24; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “High Tor”: Maxwell Anderson, 1938 Fall; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “Lost Horizons”: Harry Segal and John Hayden, 1938 Fall; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “The Best Cure”: Belmont-Ashton, 1938 December 28; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “The Man of Destiny”: G. B. Shaw, 1939 March 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “Androcles and the Lion”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - “The Fireman's Flame: John Van Antwerp, 1939 April 25; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Illinois, 1939 April 15-July 25; 1 folder
    - “The Swing Mikando”: Harry Minturn, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - “Othello”: Shakespeare, 1939 April 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - “Hamlet”: Shakespeare, 1939 July 25; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Federal Ballet, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Iowa, 1919 June 3-1937 May 27; 1 folder
    - “Class of '29”: Orrie Lashin and Milo Hastings, 1937 April 22; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “The Class of '29”: Orrie Lashin and Milo Hastings, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Then Minute Alibi”: Anthony Armstrong, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Pursuit of Happiness”: Laurence and Armina Marshall Langner, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Pursuit of Happiness”: Laurence and Armina Marshall Langner, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Old Autumn”: James Knox Miller, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Up Pops the Devil”: Albert Hackett and Frances Goodrich, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Blind Alley”: James Warwick, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Blind Alley”: James Warwick, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “The Royal Family”: George Kaufman and Edna Ferber, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Help Yourself”: Paul Vulpius, 1937 April 29; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Brothers”: Herbert Ashton Jr, 1919 June 3-7; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “Rachel's Man”: Bradbury Foote, 1937 May 27; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - “It Can't Happen Here”: John C. Moffitt and Sinclair Lewis, 1937 May 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Louisiana, 1938 September 14-1939 April 16; 1 folder
    - “The Drunkard”: W. H. Smith, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “Autumn Crocus”: C. L. Anthony, 1938 September 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “Autumn Crocus”: C. L. Anthony, 10/5, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “Whistling in the Dark”: Laurence Gross and Edward Childs Carpenter, 1938 October 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “If Ye Break Faith”: Maria M. Coxe, 1938 November 21; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “The Best Cure”: Belmont-Ashton, 1938 December 12; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “Prologue to Glory”: E. P. Conkle, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - “Within theses Walls”: Marcus L. Bach, 1939 April 16; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Maine, 1938-1939; 1 folder
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 August 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 August 9; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 August 18; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 August 19; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 September 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 September 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 September 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1938; 1938 October 1; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 October 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 October 11; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 October 21; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 15; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 16; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 17; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 22; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 23; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 24; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 25; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 November 28; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 December 2; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 December 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 December 5; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 December 9; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue (Fall), 1938 January 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1939; 1938 February 23; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1939; 1938 March 25; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1939; 1938 April 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Big Vaudeville Musical Revue, 1939; 1938 April 21; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts, 1938 August 17-1939 April 14; 1 folder
    - Light Operas: Gilbert and Sullivan, 3/7, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Macbeth”: Shakespeare, 1/31, no year; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Boy Meet Girl”: Bella and Samuel Spewack, 1938 August 24; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Scampolo”: Dario Niccodami, 12/2, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Doctor Faustus”: Marlowe, 11/22, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Doctor Faustus”: Marlowe, 11/17, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Dus Groise Gevins,”, 1938 November 21; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Dus Groise Gevins,”, 1938 December 12; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “The Barton Mystery”: Walter Hackett, 1939 January 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “The Barton Mystery”: Walter Hackett, 1939 February 16; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “The Barton Mystery”: Walter Hackett, 1939 April 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Juan Jose”: Joaquin Dicenta, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Juan Jose”: Joaquin Dicenta, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Macbeth”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “The Drunkard”: W. H. Smith, 1938 September; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Haiti”: William du Bois, 10/4, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Pinocchio”: Yasha Frank, 4/11, no year; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - “Return to Death”: P. Washington Porter, 1938 August 17; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Michigan, 1938 December; 1 folder
    - “The Locked Room”: Herbert Ashton Jr, 1938 December; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - “The Merry Wives of Windsor”: Shakespeare, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - New Hampshire, dates not examined; 1 folder
    - “Ye Old Timers Minstrel and Vaudeville Revue”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “The Best Cure”: Belmont Ashton, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “Accent on Youth”: Samson Raphaelson, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “American Wings”: Talbot Jennings, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “Vaudeville Revue”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “The Roundabout”: J. B. Priestly, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “The Barton Mystery”: Walter Hackett, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “Hotel Limit and Vaudeville Revue”, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - “On Stage”: Benjamin M. Kaye, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - New York, 1936-1938; portions of 2 boxes
    - “Murder in the Cathedral”: T. S. Eliot, dates not examined; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Class of '29”: Orrie Lashin and Milo Hastings, dates not examined; 4 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “The Sun and I”: Barrie and Leona Stavis, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Help Yourself”: Paul Vulpius, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “American Holiday”: Edwin L. and Albert Baker, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Murder in the Cathedral”: T. S. Eliot, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Help Yourself”: Paul Vulpius, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “The Path of Flowers”: Valentine Katayev, dates not examined; 4 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Battle Hymn”: Michael Blankfort and Michael Gold, dates not examined; 5 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Battle Hymn”: Michael Blankfort and Michael Gold, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Battle Hymn”: Michael Blankfort and Michael Gold, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Native Ground”: Virgil Geddes, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Native Ground”: Virgil Geddes, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Native Ground”: Virgil Geddes, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Chalk Dust”: Harold A. Clarke and Maxwell Nurnberg, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Chalk Dust”: Harold A. Clarke and Maxwell Nurnberg, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “The Cherokee Night”: Lynn Riggs, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Tobias and the Angel”: James Bridie, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “The Ballad of Davy Crockett”: H. R. Hays, dates not examined; 2 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - “Doctor Faustus”: Marlowe, dates not examined; 3 copies (Box 2, Folder 14)